(If you don't want to get reported,
come running quickly.)
"Proxy Driver"
(Episode 2)
Please, come in.
Actually, I asked to see you
because I wanted to apologize.
What?
Please, have a seat first.
That day, I found out...
my wife was having an affair.
I was so drunk.
I wasn't in my right mind.
Oh, thank god.
I thought you were some creep.
I'm not that kind of person.
It was actually my wife's birthday.
I'd even planned a surprise...
But suddenly being all alone,
it was so scary and lonely.
I had no one to call.
You were the only one
I could think of.
But you really scared me back there.
You scared me to death.
I'm sorry.
To make it up to you,
Let me pour you a drink.
No, it's okay.
I should probably go now.
Please, stay just a moment.
I don't know what I might do.
Alright, then.
I'll stay for a little while.
We met three years ago.
No matter how much I messed up,
she always said she loved me.
But yesterday...
I went to her church,
and saw her in bed with the pastor.
I loved that bitch so much.
I really, truly loved her.
I loved her so much, that bitch!
How could she do this to me?
To me
What do I...
What do I do?
Please, help me.
It's my first time. I have to go.
So what, you bitch?
So what?